<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sir Apollo Kaggwa Primary School - kitintale</title>
    <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sir Apollo Kaggwa Primary School - kitintale</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:05:20 +0330</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sir Apollo Kaggwa Kitintale Rolls Out ‘Yummy Friday’ to Foster Nutrition, Joy, and All-Round Growth</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/2025-06-07-sir-apollo-kaggwa-kitintale-rolls-out-yummy-friday-to-foster-nutrition-joy-and-all-round-growt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 22:05:20 +0330</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/2025-06-07-sir-apollo-kaggwa-kitintale-rolls-out-yummy-friday-to-foster-nutrition-joy-and-all-round-growt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sir Apollo Kaggwa Primary School Kitintale is delighted to unveil &amp;lsquo;&lt;strong&gt;Yummy Friday&lt;/strong&gt;,&amp;rsquo; a thoughtful and learner-centered initiative tailored to enrich the well-being and development of our beloved kindergarten pupils. Though designed as a joyful Friday experience, the official launch was held on Thursday, June 5, 2025, to accommodate the national public holiday on Friday, June 6, 2025. This strategic move ensures every child enjoys the full benefit of this exciting program from the very beginning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sir Apollo Kaggwa Primary School Kitintale Commemorates Uganda Martyrs Day in a Spirit-Filled Skit</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/2025-06-02-sir-apollo-kaggwa-primary-school-kitintale-commemorates-uganda-martyrs-day-in-a-spirit-filled-skit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 21:02:27 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/2025-06-02-sir-apollo-kaggwa-primary-school-kitintale-commemorates-uganda-martyrs-day-in-a-spirit-filled-skit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This afternoon, Sir Apollo Kaggwa Primary School Kitintale came alive with a spirit of reverence and reflection as learners, teachers, and staff gathered to commemorate Uganda Martyrs Day. The event was marked by a heart-stirring skit presented by the Primary Six Christian pupils, who brought to life the powerful story of Uganda’s most celebrated saints. With grace and solemnity, the pupils paid tribute to the brave young men who chose death over denying their faith, leaving the audience in awe of their conviction and courage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Employment Opportunities at Sir Apollo Kaggwa Schools</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/employment-opportunities-at-sirapollokaggwaschools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 06:57:00 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/employment-opportunities-at-sirapollokaggwaschools/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sir Apollo Kaggwa Schools&lt;/strong&gt;, established in 1996, is seeking qualified and enthusiastic professionals to join their dynamic team. This is your opportunity to become part of a reputable institution committed to delivering quality education.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;available-positions&#34;&gt;Available Positions&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are hiring for the following roles:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;table&gt;&#xA;  &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Number of Staff&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;          &lt;th&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Qualification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Teachers (Science, Social Studies, English, Mathematics)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;80&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Diploma in Primary Education (Credit or Distinction)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Teachers (Lower Section)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;30&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Grade III + Certificate in ECD (Credit or Distinction)&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Secretaries&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Graduate&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Nurses&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Diploma&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Caregivers&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;20&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Certificate in ECD&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Chefs&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;15&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;td&gt;Certificate&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Important Notes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahirire Faith Crowned Little Miss Tourism 2023 2024</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/ahirire-faith-crowned-little-miss-tourism-2023-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 13:00:58 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/ahirire-faith-crowned-little-miss-tourism-2023-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce that our pupil, Ahirire Faith, has been crowned Little Miss Tourism for the year 2023-2024. Ahirire represented Sir Apollo Kaggwa Schools with grace and confidence throughout the competition, showcasing not only her beauty but also her intelligence and talent.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This remarkable achievement reflects the excellence and holistic development fostered at our schools. Join us in congratulating Ahirire Faith on this well-deserved honor!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sir Apollo Kaggwa Scools Kisaasi Carbinet Courtesy Visit Speaker Parliament</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/sir-apollo-kaggwa-scools-kisaasi-carbinet-courtesy-visit-speaker-parliament/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:54:37 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/sir-apollo-kaggwa-scools-kisaasi-carbinet-courtesy-visit-speaker-parliament/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Kisaasi Cabinet of Sir Apollo Kaggwa Schools recently had the privilege of paying a courtesy visit to the Speaker of Parliament. This visit provided our students with a unique opportunity to engage with one of the highest offices in the country, learn about the legislative process, and discuss matters of importance to our school community.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We extend our gratitude to the Speaker for welcoming us and fostering dialogue with our future leaders. Such experiences contribute to the holistic development of our students and instill in them a sense of civic responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inter Sir Apollo Kaggwa Schools Swimming Gala</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/inter-sir-apollo-kaggwa-schools-swimming-gala/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:54:15 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/inter-sir-apollo-kaggwa-schools-swimming-gala/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce the upcoming Inter Sir Apollo Kaggwa Schools Swimming Gala scheduled to take place on April 2nd, 2024. This event promises to be a day filled with friendly competition and camaraderie as students from different branches of our schools come together to showcase their swimming skills.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We invite all students, parents, and supporters to join us for this exciting event and cheer on our talented swimmers. Stay tuned for more updates and highlights from the gala!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Participation in Mini Fuba National Basketball Tournament</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/participation-in-mini-fuba-national-basketball-tournament/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 12:53:55 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/posts/participation-in-mini-fuba-national-basketball-tournament/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sir Apollo Kaggwa Schools recently participated in the Mini FUBA National Basketball Tournament held in Kampala. The tournament brought together schools from across the country to compete in various categories. Our students showcased exceptional skills and sportsmanship throughout the event, reflecting the dedication and training provided by our coaching staff.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more updates on our sports achievements!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/img/about1.webp&#34; alt=&#34;About Us Image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;school-profile&#34;&gt;School Profile&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sir Apollo Kaggwa Primary School – Kitintale is a private day mixed school registered with the ministry of education and sports with a UNEB centre number offering Education to Ugandan and non-Ugandan children based on the Ugandan syllabus and equipping them with necessary life skills.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;school-motto&#34;&gt;School Motto&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our School Motto is: “Education with a Purpose”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mission-statement&#34;&gt;Mission Statement&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The school mission statement is “to provide a stimulating and credible learning environment which will produce dynamic and talented young Ugandan citizens and ensure all learners are equipped to meet the challenges of life”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alumni</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/alumni/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Application Form</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/admission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/admission/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Form Submitted</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/success.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/success.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAD PREFECT’S MESSAGE</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/hp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/hp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;head-prefects-message&#34;&gt;HEAD PREFECT’S MESSAGE&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Fellow Pupils, Teachers, Parents, and Esteemed Visitors,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Greetings to you all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am truly honored to serve as the Guild President of Sir Apollo Kaggwa Primary School Kitintale. As a pupil leader, I take pride in representing a school that inspires us to be disciplined, focused, and confident in everything we do, both in class and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Our school is a special place where every child is supported to do their best. The teachers work diligently to make learning interesting and meaningful. Through classwork, group activities, and guidance, we are consistently encouraged to aim higher and never give up. I am grateful to be part of a school that believes in the success of every learner.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HEAD TEACHER&#39;S MESSAGE</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/hm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/hm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;head-teachers-welcome-message&#34;&gt;Head Teacher’s Welcome Message&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Pupils, Parents, Guardians, Staff, Alumni, and Esteemed Visitors,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is with immense pride and heartfelt joy that I welcome you to Sir Apollo Kaggwa Primary School – Kitintale. Here, we cultivate a vibrant and inclusive learning community where academic excellence, moral integrity, and holistic development intertwine to shape the leaders of tomorrow. Our school is not merely a place of education, but a nurturing environment that fosters growth and exploration. Each child is cherished as a unique individual, supported through their academic and personal journeys, and empowered to reach their highest potential. We believe that education is a partnership, and together we create a foundation for success that extends well beyond the classroom.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parent Testimonials</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/testimonial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/testimonial/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>School Motto Vision and Mission</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/motto-vission-mission/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/motto-vission-mission/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TEACHERS AND STAFF</title>
      <link>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kitintale.sirapollokaggwaschools.co.ug/staff/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The school prides itself on having a highly competent and qualified staff dedicated to nurturing both the academic and moral development of its learners. This holistic approach aims to cultivate well-rounded individuals, equipped not only with knowledge but also with the values essential for success in life. The commitment to fostering such growth reflects the institution&amp;rsquo;s vision of shaping future leaders who are both academically proficient and morally grounded.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the helm of this capable team is the headmaster, Mr. Seruyange Mathias. With extensive experience managing both private and government-aided schools, Mr. Mathias brings a wealth of knowledge to the role. His leadership style emphasizes collaboration and continuous improvement, inspiring staff to strive for excellence in their teaching practices. Under his guidance, the school has developed a positive and productive learning environment, promoting professional development for all staff members.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
